(Amy:)I've never seen him
this happy before.
It's because you've never seen him on
"Restock the Medicine Cabinet Day."
Look!
(Sheldon:)A new topical
antihistamine with lidocaine.
Wow!
(Sheldon:)I can't wait until I get a rash.
(Leonard:)Oh, Gas-X has a new ultra strength.
(Leonard:)I guess they really do
read their mail.
(Sheldon:)Hey, isn't that Professor Proton?
(Leonard:)Oh, yeah.
(Sheldon:)Look at him, just standing in line,
(Sheldon:)like he wasn't moderately
famous 30 years ago.
(Sheldon:)Let's go say hello.
(Leonard:)Oh, maybe we shouldn't bother him.
(Sheldon:)I'm not going to bother him,
I'm going to talk to him.
(Leonard:)He thinks there's a difference.
(Sheldon:)Arthur?
(Sheldon:)Arthur, it's me, Sheldon Cooper.
(Sheldon:)You may not remember
because of your advanced age.